{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_1_9VM6I7",
                "player_12_9VM6I7",
                "player_11_9VM6I7",
                "player_3_9VM6I7",
                "player_10_9VM6I7",
                "player_6_9VM6I7"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                1,
                12,
                11,
                3,
                10,
                6
            ],
            "animation": [
                "pick_up",
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "liedown",
                "liedown",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man with medium skin, wearing sunglasses, maroon polo shirt, beige pants, brown shoes, and a watch",
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    1534.278,
                    -1282.364,
                    95.025,
                    0.0,
                    0.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    1947.337,
                    -1128.893,
                    94.881,
                    0,
                    -169.41895632372146,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    1881.595,
                    -843.693,
                    93.275,
                    0,
                    -45.23606390742003,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    1930.414,
                    -1263.541,
                    95.037,
                    0,
                    -90.88379868300544,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    1774.338,
                    -1339.823,
                    95.183,
                    0,
                    117.85639374646212,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    1597.807,
                    -1366.332,
                    94.782,
                    0,
                    43.43169523480756,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            1626.847,
            -1240.018,
            94.782
        ],
        "sample_radius": 671.1393850847115
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            1488.072,
            -1842.672,
            94.966,
            0,
            65.60814035208695,
            0
        ],
        [
            1969.292,
            -433.26,
            127.515,
            0,
            -103.96289739826676,
            0
        ],
        [
            2537.412,
            -1444.169,
            38.605,
            0,
            162.465556748222,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is farther from the_man_in_white_shirt, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_burgundy_polo_and_light_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_woman_in_black_vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_woman_in_black_vest"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "six"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are lying down on the snow?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many people are engaged in holding an object?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many men are depicted in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many women are present among the individuals?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many men in the scene are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding an object",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. lying down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in a grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. lying down"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in a white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouching"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in a deep V-top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "C. lying down"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in a burgundy polo and light pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. walking"
                ],
                "answer": "C. lying down"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in a black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. sitting",
                    "C. lying down",
                    "D. crouching"
                ],
                "answer": "A. standing"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the back-right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-right of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in burgundy polo and light pants relative to the man in light pants and sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the back-left of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. In front of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the back-left of"
            }
        }
    }
}